templateflip.com 2019-01-19

# Privacy Policy - TemplateFlip

This privacy policy applies to TemplateFlip.com and all its subdomains, associated services and applications.

If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

TemplateFlip.com respects your privacy and is committed to protect your personal information. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by TemplateFlip.com and how it is used.

We may publish updates to our policy from time to time.

### Analytics and Log files

Like many other Web sites, TemplateFlip.com makes use of log files and analytics. The information includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Storage

We use cookies and web storage to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to users on TemplateFlip.com based on their visit to TemplateFlip.com and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of these cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on TemplateFlip.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. TemplateFlip.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
